A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1955-1983; 1; 58.87 Cubic Feet 155 letter-size document boxes. Boxes 1-155.
  - A-B-C-D
    - DiVirgilio, Nicholas (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Dixon, Edward (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Dixon, Paul (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Djokic, Pierre (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Dlugoszewski, Lucia (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Doane, David (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Dobriansky, Andrij (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Dodds, David (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Doe, Edward (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Doggett, Lorraine (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Dohrmann, Edward (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Dolan, Cornelia (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Dolph, Nancy (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Domanski, Pauline (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Domb, Daniel (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Domenici, Gianna (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Dominguez, Albert (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Donahue, Mary Lou (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Donohue, Brian (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Donohue, Dwyla (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Dooley, Richard (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Doolittle, Patricia (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Doppmann, William (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Doran, Isabella (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Dordick, Johanna (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Dore, Ruth (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Dorenfeld, Joanne (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Dorfman, Joseph (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Doro, Mariana (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Dorsey, Lauretta (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Doss, Gale Ronald (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Doster, Paul Watson (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Dougherty, Lee (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Douglas, Conrad (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Doulis, Maria (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Douglas, Dwaine S. (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Doussant, Herbert (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Dowis, Jeaneane (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Roger and Derry Drinkall (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Drake, Paulina (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Drake, Willie Ken (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Dreyfus, Laurence (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Driver, Robert (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Drummond, Margaret, Ann (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Dubin, Liane (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Dubow, Marilyn (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Dudley, Raymond (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Duesing, Dale (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Dufault, Mary Elizabeth (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Dukes, John (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Dumas, Andrea (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Dunbar, Clark (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Dunbar, Walter (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Dunham, Sister Memeve (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Dunkel, Paul (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Dunlap, John Robert (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Dunn, Alan (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Dunn, Mignon (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Dunning, Catherine (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Dunscombe, Harry (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Dupree, William (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Dutcher, Alice (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Dutro, Ronald (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Dutt, Mohan C. (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Duvall, William (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Duykers, John (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Dwyer (Bennett), Sharon (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Dwyer, Thomas (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Dyen, Doris (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Dyslin, Susann (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - E-F-G-H
    - Ealy, Susan Whedon (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Earls, Paul (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Earnest, David (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Early Music Institute, Inc. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Early Music Laboratory (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - East Harlem Tenants Council (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Earp, Lawrence (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - East, Thomas (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Washington State College (Moldenhauser Archives) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Eastman, Julius (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Eberl, Carl (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Ebert, Carl (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Ebert, Peter (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Echols, Paul C. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Eddy, Timothy (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Edel, Theodore (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Edgar, Raphael (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Edgemon, Sharon (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Edmunds, John (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Educational Alliance (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Edwards, Carole (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Edwards, Eleanor (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Edwards, Elizabeth (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Edwards, George (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Edwards, Ryan (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Edwards, Sheila (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Effenbach, Leah (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Effron, David L. (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Eastern Opera Theatre (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Eger, Joseph (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Egerton, Hugh (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Ehrlich, Paul (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Eichel, Paul (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Eichen, Bernard (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Eichorn, William (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Eikenberry, Wayne (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Eisenberg, Phillip M. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Electric Symphony Orchestra Company (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Elgar, Anne (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Eliasen, Mikael (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Ellis, Brent (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Ellis, Van Zandt (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Ellison, Dorothy (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Ellsworth, Glen (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Elsey, Bonnieray (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Elstein, Carl (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Elvira, Pablo (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Elyn, Mark (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Emanuel, Dawin (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Emerson, Isabelle (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Emoed, Laszlo (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Emoed-Wallace, Julia (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Empire Sinfonietta (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Empire State Music Festival, Inc. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Endich, Saramae (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - England, Nicholas (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Englebright, Lucille (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - English, Anne (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - English, Rose (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Enrico, Eugene (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - The Ensemble (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Entriken, Daniel (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Epperson, Bryan (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Epstein, Daniel (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Epstein, Selma (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Erb, James (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Erede, Christopher (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Ericksen, Edward (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Erickson, Ronald (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Ericson, Jill (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Eros, Peter (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Ervin, Karen (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Erwin, Stuart (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Eskin, Virginia (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Estes, Simon L. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - European Auditions, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - European Auditions, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - European Auditions, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - European Auditions, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - European Auditions, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - European Auditions, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - European Auditions, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - European Auditions, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Evans, Allan (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Evans, David F. III (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Evans, Peter H. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Phillip (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Evera, Nancy Catherine (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Eves, Rosemary (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Ewing, Maria (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Fabre, Richard (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Fair, Joseph (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Fairfield County Summer Music School (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Falck, Robert A. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Falco, Anthony (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Falcon, Ruth (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Falcone, Mary Lou (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Falconer, Joan Ormsby (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Falgoust, Rosemary (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Falke, Kirsten (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Farber, Bonnie Bogle (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Farberman, Harold, New Arts Orchestra (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Farkas, Alexander (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Farley, Carole (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Farmer, Elizabeth (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Farnworth, Ralph (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Farr, Anne (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Farr, Lowell (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Farr, Naomi (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Farrar, Ann (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Farrar, James (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Farrar, Reginald (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Farras, Helene (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Farrell, Frances (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Farrow, Norman (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Fasciano, Maria (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Faulconner, Bruce (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Fazah, Adib (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Feder, Donn-Alexandre (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Federal Music Society (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Rocky Mountain States, Inc. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Feist, Robert (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fendya, John (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Ferencz, Brenda (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Ferguson, Gene (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Fernandez, Esther (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Ferrante, John (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Ferre, Lucretia (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Ferriero, Maria (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Ferro, Daniel (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Festival of the Americas (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Festival Foundation, 1970-1978 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Festival Foundation, 1963-1969 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Festival Foundation, 1956-1962 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Festival of Opera (Laguna Beach) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Festival Opera Theater, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Festival Opera Theater, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Festival Opera Theater, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Festival Opera Theater, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Festival Opera Theater, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - The Festival Orchestra Society, Inc., 1964-1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fetta, Frank (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Fey, Richard (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Fields, Ethel (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Figueroa, Yvonne (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Finell, Alan (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Finkelstein, Zitta (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Finnley, Marvin (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Fiorillo, Alexander (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Fiorito, John (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Fischer, Elizabeth (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Fishbein, Zenon (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Fisher, Earl (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Flam, Eugene (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Flavin, William Thomas (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Fleck, William (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Fleetwood, James (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fleming, John (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Fleming, Sarah (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Fletcher, Daniel (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Flissler, Joyce (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Floer, Rikard (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Flowers, Martha (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Foldi, Andrew (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Ford, Gene (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Foreman, Thomas (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Forero, Luis (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Forney, William Dean (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Forsmo, Ronald (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Forstat, Milton (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Fortune, George G., Jr. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Foster, Lawrence (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Foster, Leesa (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Fox, Frederick (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Foxworth, James (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Foye, Hope (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Fraenkel, Jean B. (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Franceschi, Vera (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Francesco, Philip (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Francis, John Bruce (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Frank, Claude (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Frank, Janet (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Franklin, DeLance (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Franz Liszt Sesquicentennial Committee (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Frederick, Carole (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Fredricks, Richard (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Free Library of Philadelphia (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Freeman, James (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Freeman, Robert (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Freeman, Ron (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Freeman, Stephanie (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Freier, Shalheveth (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Freireich, Betty (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Freitag, Wolfgang (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Frick, Raymond (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Friday, Raymond (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Fried, Howard (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Carl Friedberg Music Foundation (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Friederich, Sylvia (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Friedheim, Philip, NYU (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Friedman, Eric (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Friedman, Viktor (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Friends of French Opera, Inc. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Frierson, Andrew (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Frost, Thomas (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Fromme, James (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Fryer Sisters String Trio (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Fuenterosa, Sondra (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Fuks, Mauricio (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Fulbright Commission - Germany (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Fuller, Frederick (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Fuschi, Olegna (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Futran, Margarete (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Gabriel, Bernard (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Gaburo, Kenneth (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Gaffney, Dorothy (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Gage, Irwin (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Gagliano, Sandra (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Gaither, Mareda (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Gale, Sheila (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Galiano, Joseph (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Galitsis, William (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Gannon, James (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Gansz, George (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Gantt, Hermann (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Garabedian, Lillian (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Garcia, Flor (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Gardner, Guy (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Gardner Museum, Isabella S., Boston, MA (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Gargani, Gloria (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Garland, Harry (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Garniez, Nancy (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Garson, Jeanne (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Gartside, Robert (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Gates, Earl W., University of North Carolina (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Gates, Pamela (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Gause, Laphalia (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Gauthier, Eva (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Gavoorian, Joan (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Geary, Barbara (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Geiger, Ruth (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Geith, Kathryn (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Gentry, Lula P. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - George, Barbara (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - George, Edna May (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Gerber, Edward (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Gerber, Joyce (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Gerbrands, Ronald (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Gerhart, Martha (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Geringer, Rose (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Gerle, Robert (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Gesensway, Louis (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Gershefski, Martha (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Gersten, Frederick (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Gewald, Robert (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Giancotti, Anna (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Giannini, Mme. Dusolina (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Gilbert, Ramon (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Gillaspy, John (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Gilleran, James (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Gillespie, Robert (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Gillette, Bennie Jean (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Gilliam, Viola (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Gilmore, Earl (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Gilston, Frank (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Ginn, Sophie (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Giordano, Elena (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Giusti, Norma (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Glanville-Hicks, Peggy (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Glasser, Ruth (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Glaze, Gary (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Glazer, Frank (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Glover, Carrie (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Godes, Herman (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Godfrey, Batyah (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Godt, Irving (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Goeke, Leo Francis (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Goeller, Vera (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Goethe Institute (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Goldberger, David (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Golden, Richard (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Goldovsky Opera Theater (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Goldstein, Ella (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Gomberg, Robert A. (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Goodall, Valorie (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Goodlake, Richard (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Goodloe, Robert (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Goodman, George (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Goodman, Janet (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Gorder, Suzanne (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Gordon, Barbara (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Cecelia B. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Gordon, Edith (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Gordon, Priscilla (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Gordon, Stewart (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Goss, Robert (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Gotham Barogue Ensemble (Stoddard Lincoln) (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Goucher College (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Gould, Murray (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Governmental Affairs Institute, Russia (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Graf, Werner (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Graff, Anne (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Graham, Daniel (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Graham, Jean (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Graham, William Harvey (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Granat, Endre (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Grant, Dale (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Grant, Gordon (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Grant, Jeanne (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Grant, Robert (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Gratovich, Eugene (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Gray, Wendell (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Grealish, Jeanne (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Greater Trenton Symphony Association (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Green, Eugene (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Green, Lee (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Green, Roslita (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Greene, William (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Greenlee, Anita (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Greenspon, Muriel (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Greenwell, Charles (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Greenwich House (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Gregori, Robert (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Gregory, James (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Grice, Gary (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Griffel, Kay (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Griffeth, Julie (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Grillo, Joann (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Grimaldi, Angela (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Grist, Reri (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Grobe, Donald (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gross, William (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Grosz, Mikulas (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Group for New Music - Portland (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Grubb, Thomas (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Guarnieri, John A., Jr. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Guazzerotti, John (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Guggenheim John Simon Memorial Foundation (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Guggenheim Museum - 20 Century Music Series (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Gugliotta, Anne (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Guinn, Mr. Leslie (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Gundy, Carolyn (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Gunn, John Paul (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Gunter, Jane (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Guralnik, Robert (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Gurley, Wilburt (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Gustern, Josef (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Gutche, Gene (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Guthrie, William (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Gutoff, Daniel (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Guttman, Yehuda (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Gyori, Jules (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Haber, John B. (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Hadley-Robinson, Marie (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Hageman, John Thomas (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Hageman, Sara Rhodes (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Hagen, Betty-Jean (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Hagenah, Elizabeth (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Hagopian, Maryam (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Hale, Robert (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Haley, Hope (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Hailman, Ludlow (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Hall, Joyce (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Hall, Marjorie (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Ham, David (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Brett (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Hamilton, Robert (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Hamilton, Roy (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Hamilton, William A. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Hammar, Martha (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Hammerman, Heinz (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Hammond, Frederick (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Hampe, Arlene (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Hampton, Bonnie (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Han, Tong II (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Handel Festival, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Handel and Haydn Society (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Hanisch, Iris (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Hankla, Donna (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Hanley, William (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Hansell, Sven (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Hanson, Michael (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Hara, Kazuko (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Haraldson, Marian (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Harbachick, Stephen (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Harden, Gretta (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Hardie, Graham (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Harlem Philharmonic Society, Inc. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Harlem School of the Arts (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Harlowe, Lee (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Harned, Shirley Lee (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Haroutunian, Sarah (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Harper, Elinor (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Harpsichord Music Society (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Harrington, Grace (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Harris, Charles (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Harris, Hilda (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Harris, John Albert (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Harrison, Michael (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Harrison, Victoria (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Harrower and Calloway (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Harsanyi, Janice (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Hart, Ray (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Hartford Festival of Music (Robert Brawley) (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Harth, Sidney (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Harvard Glee Club (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Hartzell, Lois (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Harvey, Kenneth (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Haskins, Alfred (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Haspel, Barbara (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Haupt, Charles (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Haverford Summer Institute and Festival of Chamber Music (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Hawkins, Lucia (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Hawkins, Terrence (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Hawley, Alexandra (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Hawthorne, Jim (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Hawthorne, Joseph (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Hayes, Marvin (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Hayman, Richard (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Haynes, Eugene (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Hays, Warren (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Hayward, Thomas (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Heafner, Carolyn (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Heafner, Jean (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Hecht, Joshua (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Hedges, Delight (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Hedlund, Ronald (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Heilbut, Francis (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Heimall, Linda (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Heinson, Lise (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Heller, Jerome (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Heller, Lissy (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Henderson, Donald G., University of Michigan (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Henery, Diana (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Henninger, Bernhard M. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Henninger, Nancy (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Henry Street Settlement (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Hensel, Howard (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Hensley, Mary (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Hebert, Pamela (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Herford, Julius (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Herlinger, Jan (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Hernandez, Edita (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Hernandez, Ivette (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Hernandez, Orlando (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Herdan, Tibor (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Herndon, Arthur (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Herndon, Thomas (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Herrnkind, Edward (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Hersh, Paul (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Hess, Dame Myrs Trust (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Hewitt, Peter (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Heyer, Jean Ann (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Heyne, Dr. William (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Hicks, Hervey (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - HI Enterprises (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Higgison, Peyton (Bruce Peyton) (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - High Tor Opera Company (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Highley, Ronald and Joanne (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Hill, Douglas (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Hill, Mildred (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Hill, Stephen Jackson (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Hills, George Arthur (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Hillman, Erik (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Hilse, Walter (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Hilton, Shirley (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Hinckley, Alexandra (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Hinderas, Natalie (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Hinds, Esther C. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Hindsley, Charles (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Hines, Theodore (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Hirsh, Norma (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Hirst, Grayson (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Hodes, Gloria (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Hodges, Ronald (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Hoekstra, Gerald (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Hoffman, Jay K. (Box 57, Folder 13)